Ada, create two claw code agents. Name
them Sony and Blink.
>> Understood, Dan. I'll create two Claude
code agents named Sony and Blink.
Both agents Sony and Blink are ready.
Dan, what tasks should we assign them
next?
>> Command Sony to read all files in the AI
docs directory. Use the plan/comand
to support video generation using the
Soore API. Make sure that it writes its
plan to the specs directory.
>> Got it, Dan. I'll have Sony read all
files in the AI docs directory. Then
plan for video generation support using
the Sora API and save the plan in the
specs directory. Sony is working on it.
Dan, let me know if you want to assign
something to Blink next.
>> Ada command blink to invert the primary
colors and the front end. We want black
text on a white background. Pull in the
play font from Google Fonts and apply it
to all text.
>> Understood, Dan. I'll instruct Blink to
invert the primary colors in the front
end for black text on a white background
and then apply the play font from Google
fonts to all text. Anything else you
want to line up?
>> The tech industry wants you to pick one
model, one provider, one tool. But for
you and I, the engineer, this is a
losing game. Why is that? It's because
you're optimizing for their business
model, not your maximum capability.
Loyalty in the generative AI age is not
the winning strategy. The winning play
is to use them all. Think in ands, not
ors. Use Gemini models, red next OpenAI
models. Use cloud code next to the
OpenAI's real-time API. Combine, mix,
and mash. So, what if you took this idea
further and put together three
state-of-the-art generative AI
technologies into one big three super
agent?
Let me show you how this works. This is
highly experimental. I've built out
these multi- aent systems in the past.
This one is by far the most powerful.
Let me show you exactly how. Ada, list
our current agents.
>> Sure, Dan. We currently have two active
agents, Sony and Blink.
>> All right. Can you go ahead and check
the status of Blink? How's it doing with
this updates?
>> Dan, Blink's task is underway. It's
identified the files and is beginning
implementation to invert colors and
apply the play font.
>> Okay, fantastic. What about Sony? Sony
has completed reviewing the AI docs and
backend architecture and it's now
planning the full Sora API integration.
We'll check back soon once it progresses
further.
>> Couple quick things to mention right
away. Right, we have an orchestrator
voice agent. After you have better
agents, you add more agents and then you
start building custom agents. You need a
wrapper to actually communicate and
control all of your agents. Right next
to our voice orchestrator agent, we also
have multi- aent observability. Right?
You can see we have a live pulse of all
of our agents activities. If we open
this up, you can see this in even more
detail. We're leveraging cloud code
hooks to get great details out of every
one of our agents. And you can see here
one of our agents is now validating its
work with the new Gemini 2.5 computer
use model inside of a new agent inside
of a tool. We'll break that down in just
a second here. We'll walk through the
architecture. Our agent is actually
validating its work here, right? So, I'm
just going to move this off screen so I
can finish up. You can see that tool use
getting fired off right there. Blink is
actually validating its work with a
browser agent. So very powerful stuff
right out of the gate. Our agents are
more powerful than ever. And thanks to
multi- aent observability. We can
actually see what they're doing right
without being stuck in the loop. This is
a huge huge trend that is going to be
relevant as we move forward in the
generative AI age. As agentic engineers,
if you can't see what your agents are
doing at scale, you will not be able to
scale your compute. And when you scale
your compute, you scale your impact.
Something else really cool here just to
mention with this multi- aent
observability UI, we are also getting
quick, fast, cheap model summaries. You
can see this work coming in in the
background. We're getting cheap, fast
model summaries of every command coming
in here, right? So, we don't need to dig
into everything. Of course, we can if we
want to. We can see the entire payload,
but what we really want is highlevel.
You know, we only want to dive in if
something goes wrong. Here's another
browser agent confirming that color
change, right? We have powerful closed
loop structures. Our cloud code agent
has a computer use tool that it can use
to actually completely validate its
work. Then the browser tool will spit
back out any, you know, success or
failure messages. Again, I'm just going
to get this out the way here. And our
agent will then validate its work. So,
Blink is testing its work and I think
right now Sony has completed its work
actually. So, let's go ahead and see how
Sony's doing. Let's just check our
primary interface here. And yeah, check
this out. Agent Sony result message task
complete. And there's the breakdown. So,
I'm going to confirm this with ADA, the
agent orchestrator. And then we're going
to continue building out front end and
backend for content generation. Ada, go
ahead and list our agents and check on
both of our agent statuses.
>> All right, Dan. I'll first list our
agents and then check the status of both
Sony and Blink. Dan, here's the update.
Sony has successfully completed its
task. It generated a full specification
document at Specs Sora video generation
integration. Blink has completed the
code changes, inverting colors, and
applying the play font and is about to
start the dev server for validation.
Both agents are on track and ready for
any next steps you have in mind.
>> Fantastic. Ada, go ahead and open up
that specs file generated by Sony.
>> Sure, Dan. The specs file is now open in
VS Code. Dan, let me know if you want to
review anything specific or move on to
the next task.
>> Very cool stuff here, right? We have our
agent agentically calling specific tools
that help us operate a multi- aent
system. Our Sony agent has completed
this plan for Sora video generation.
There you go. You can see architecture,
API endpoints, response request body.
You can see here it's actually got a lot
of the key information dialed in. are a
Gentic coders are of course running on
the brand new Claude Code 2 with the
Claude 4.5 sonnet model. Very powerful,
very capable, very hands-off, very
autonomous model. We talked about this
in our previous video. Cloud code is the
agentic coding tool to beat right now. A
list videos, delete video, remix.
Fantastic. So, these are all the new
features coming out of the OpenAI Sora 2
API. Here's our project structure. Great
breakdown. You might have noticed that
when I was commanding our orchestrator
to write the prompt into our Sony agent
decoding agent, I said use the slash
command plan. So, this actually ran a
custom slash command and wrote the plan
out in a structure that we've detailed.
Okay, so custom slash commands very
powerful. They come up over and over and
over again because they represent
reusable compute for your agents for
you. They allow you to set up reusable
structures of results. This looks super
great. I'm going to add one more thing
here throughout this, you know,
experiment here. I'm going to try not to
write any prompts. Okay, I'm just going
to talk to my orchestrator. I want my
orchestrator to handle things aside from
voice prompting. I don't want to type
anything except for a couple key updates
here. So, I'm just going to say
important additional notes. I want to
make sure that the self validation loop
here is really, really tight for our
agent. Be sure to set up logging
structures. This way you can validate if
issues occur. You can lean on your
output files. Python logging and best
practices. Exactly. Okay. So, this is
great. So, this plan looks fantastic.
I'm going to go ahead and just close
this now. That's been saved and updated.
And now I'm going to have Sony get to
work on actually implementing this. Ada,
instruct Sony to run the build custom/
command against the exact specification
file it generated.
>> Understood, Dan. I'll have Sony run a
build based on the exact specification
file it created. Sony is running the
build now, Dan.
>> Okay, fantastic. And then let's command
Blink to read that specification file
and report when it's done reading. No
building yet. Just have it read that
file.
>> Got it, Dan. I'll instruct Blink to read
the specification file and report back
once it's done reading. I'll send that
command now.
>> Now, in our multi-agent observability,
we're going to see those two agents kick
off.
>> Blink is now reading the specification
file, Dan. So now we have those two
agents running for us, getting worked
on, and we can quickly observe
everything that's happening here. Right?
If we just go ahead and scroll to the
bottom here, we're going to see our
agents operating. Why is this so
valuable? Why is this experiment
important to pay attention to? I think
if you're a fan of this channel, you
understand that compute is how you scale
your impact as an engineer. But we have
to keep pushing that further. First we
have better agents, then we have more
agents, then we have custom agents, and
then we need to conduct them and
orchestrate them in the best way. Blink
agent just finished. So let's command
Blink to actually start building out the
front end. Blink has read this this, you
know, 900 line plan with a detailed
breakdown of how to build the OpenAI Sor
API. We're going to have Sony focus on
the back end and now let's go ahead and
have Blink build out the front end for
this. All right, Ada command Blink to
implement the front end based on the
spec file. We want to have Sony working
on the back end like it is and we have
Blink working on the front end. Focus on
just the front end components and wiring
it up to the back end. Stick to our
black on white minimalist theme and have
a strong focus on fault tolerance and
retry logic for our video API. Does that
make sense?
>> Understood, Dan. I'll command Blink to
implement the front end components, wire
them to the back end, follow the
black-on-white theme, and ensure fault
tolerance and retry logic. I'll get that
going now.
>> Now, both of our agents are kicked off
and working, right? So we have Sony on
the back end here. And if we open up our
multi- aent observability, we can see
that exactly. So Sony is on the back
end. There's that logging setup Python
file. And now Blink is actually going to
implement on the front end. Okay. And so
two agents working. Looks great. We can
scale this up as much as we need to.
What does this application architecture
look like? Right. Let's actually just
break this down. I'll throw something on
the screen here for you as I talk
through this. It starts with the input
layer. Who are your actual drivers of
the workflow? It's the engineer. So you
or I. And then very importantly our
agents. We need to be designing input
interfaces for our agents so that they
can close the loop. All right, this is a
big big idea we talk about in tactical
agent coding. This is how you scale your
impact. Teach your agents how to correct
their own work. We then use text or
voice and the orchestrator agent is
running the OpenAI real time API. Open
AAI's real-time API starts our system
layer. So inside of our system, Realtime
API has of course several tools. And so
if we scroll back up here, you can see
some of the tools that our agent has,
right? So the tool catalog gets logged
right at the start of every session.
List agents, create agent, command
agent. These are the real big heavy
hitters. We want our agent orchestration
layer to be able to interact and command
other agents very quickly. when we
command an agent, right? When we pass a
prompt from our orchestrator agent into
our actual builder agent. So, you know,
we have claw code agents in this case.
We can also spin up browser agents,
which you'll see in a moment here. Once
we start passing in commands, this
enters the claw code world. And so,
we've done several videos, you know, sub
agents, custom/comands, infinite agentic
loops, programmatic mode, custom agents,
right? It's all there. All of that, you
know, can be truly compressed into one
command and one system that you can then
do and add additional work into. Okay.
And then the cool thing here is that our
cloud code agent has access to the new
Gemini 2.5 computer use model. It's
going to be using that agent to validate
its work and get concrete feedback in a
closed loop structure. We have closed
loop prompts built into our multi- aent
system, built into the system prompt of
our custom agent. And notice how this
orchestration layer is super thin. It
has basically crud against agents. And
we're not saying what agents exactly
here. There are any agents, right? And
they're any tool and any type. We're
going to have that new Opus model or
we're going to have that new Gemini 3
model. Whatever tool or model is coming
next, you want to be able to adapt your
system. So then we have to respond and
get actual concrete feedback. Okay? And
so that gives us our output, right?
Right. So we have the input layer, the
system layer, and then the output layer
of our multi- aent system. Also, we
should mention that our cloud code
agents are pinging out to their multi-
aent observability system. So that's all
fantastic. It's very, very powerful. Our
system then, right, via our tools and
our OpenAI real-time API, it then
outputs audio, text, files, and
basically side effects, right? Whatever
our agents have done, that's what's
going out. And then that of course loops
all the way back to us, right? The
engineer and our agents. When you're
designing these systems, you really want
to be thinking about the inputs and the
outputs and how the outputs loop back
into the inputs. Very important. It's
very critical for making the systems
powerful and legitimate. And so, you can
see here our UI just updated. Um, our
front-end agent, Blink, got some work
done here for us. This looks great. Um,
okay. And now it's updating. It's making
some UI changes, which I'm not a fan of.
I actually really like that previous uh
UI. Let me actually just go ahead and
blow this up a little bit and see what
just happened there. It had two UIs
there that overrode each other. Let's
see what's going on here. Okay, I see
Sony is actually interfering with
Blink's frontend work. So, we're
probably going to have to recommand
Blink to come back in set things up.
But, this is something that's going to
happen, right? We need clear boundaries
between our agents and our agents don't
have that, right? I wasn't clear enough
with my prompt and I wasn't clear enough
in the plan to have backend agent just
work on back-end stuff. Yeah, you can
see here Sony working on video
generation tasks. We're going to have
duplicate code here to work through.
Let's just go ahead and I'll let the
agents finish. We'll we'll see how they
kind of battle through this. Let's dive
in here and see where our agents are. We
should have given our system enough time
here. Let's go ahead and see where
things are. Ada, go ahead and give me a
status update on both of our agents.
>> Both agents are actively working. Dan,
Sony is executing its build task and
Blink is implementing the front-end
components. Both are in progress and
we'll check back for more detailed
updates soon. I'm going to go ahead and
have Blink jump back in, update the UI,
ADA, have Blink check over the new APIs
on the back end, and then set back up
the themes, styles, and components that
it initially wrote. It looks like the
Sony agent kind of also did some
front-end work, have Blink really
comprehensively look at both the front
end and the back end before it makes its
updates. We want to make sure we get
those styles back. do all that while
we're connecting to the existing
functioning API.
>> Understood, Dan.
>> So, now Blink is going to be kicked off
and uh you know, hopefully it'll
regenerate that great UI we had at the
start there. So, now we have Sony and
Blink running once again. Let's go ahead
and open this up and monitor our agents
as they work through this task. So, I am
curious at this point what Sony is
doing. I think it's just testing
through. We have some videos, we have
generation fails, download, but no
playback so far. So,
so there we go. So, that looks great.
So, Blink has updated our front end back
to that clean style. That looks awesome.
>> Glad to hear it's looking great. Dan,
let me know if you want any further
adjustments or if you'd like to proceed
with more test.
>> All right, so we have these awesome
quick templates that we can use. So, we
have our Claw Code agent testing its
workflow here. Video generator is
looking good. There we go. So, we just
saw a scroll and a image uh screenshot.
This just scroll back up.
Um, I've been really impressed with the
Gemini 2.5 computer use model. Nice. It
switched to library mode. There's a
couple of videos. Looks like these are
old videos that I've already generated
when running some tests against this.
Nice. This looks great. So, I wonder
what exactly it's testing here. I think
it's probably just doing UI tests. But
there we go. Just toggle back. I'm not
doing any of this right. By the way, my
hands are are up here.
And yeah, every time the screen kind of
flickers like that, it's actually taking
a screenshot. Thanks to our multi- aent
observability, we can see exactly the
tools that are getting kicked off. Right
now, just blink is running. So, so far
so good here. It looks like though since
it's fired off two browsers, it's
probably looking for that new connection
here. So, um I'm just going to close
this and let's see what it does here. It
might just fire up another one. And you
can see from our manual testing here, we
do have an issue. So, if we hit uh open
this, let's refresh this cinematic go
cat and then hit generate. Let's see
what we get here with some manual
testing. Okay. All right. So, we're
getting into a nice interface here.
Let's see if our queuing logic actually
works. And our agents may have marked
this as completed here. Let's let's go
ahead and see what's going on here.
Yeah. So, there's our Gemini browser
agent response. Nice video generation.
Looks like it is working there. That's
great. And here's Blink's response
message. What was done? And so,
confirmed all these are operational
cores for 3334. This is actually wrong.
It should be 333. Good. Backend front
end running on that extra port there.
That's not exactly right, but okay. So,
confirmed all endpoints. That looks
good. Uh, fantastic. Good. Testing
valid. All components are working. Our
front end does look good. Let's see how
this generation works. We do want to see
this complete. Um, but in the meantime,
what I'll do is I'll have a full-on
browser agent just spin up and run a
prompt for us. Ada, create a browser use
agent. Have that agent uh test our local
host on port 3333. Have it write a image
prompt and generate it. Make sure that
it waits for a while. It's going to take
some time to generate, but I want to
validate that this works. Make it update
the model to Sora 2 Pro. Duration 8
seconds. And let's use portrait mode.
Instruct that all to a browser use agent
after you create it.
>> Got it, Dan. I'll create a browser use
agent and instruct it to test your local
host on port 3333. Generate an image
prompt and update to Sora 2 Pro.
Duration 8 seconds. Portrait mode. I'll
make sure it waits for generation.
>> Okay. So, so this is working. So you can
see with our manual test, we did get a
cat image generated there. That looks
great. Our browser use agent is writing
that prompt by itself here. And there we
go. It's scrolling. Now it's probably
going to click uh it might click
generate video. It might update some
settings. Okay. So it's just going to
click generate video. Let's go ahead and
see what we get here. And now it's going
to run this. So as it's taking
screenshots here, it should just, you
know, run and hopefully it'll wait for
that full cycle. But in the meantime,
while that's running, check this out. We
got a full generation here. cat on a
marble table, I think.
Yeah, pretty much exactly what you would
expect, right? Uh, we can download the
thumbnail. Let's see how that works.
Fantastic. There's a thumbnail. Uh, we
can remix. We can download the sprite
sheet. That's interesting. Let's take a
look at what that looks like. Okay, so
nice. So, just a couple images
throughout the playback and create
remix. I wonder how much this works.
Okay, let's just go and try this. You
can see our video generation coming in
here for our testing agent. Um, let's
see if this video renders fully. Looks
like we might have some issues with the
browser use actually displaying the the
actual videos here. Okay, so that didn't
work. So, we'll just let that keep
spinning. So, let's remix this video.
Cat update cat to be spinning. Let's see
how this works. Okay, so I'm not sure
what happened there. It looks like our
generation legit exploded. It actually
ended our entire voice orchestration
agent, but we can go ahead and just kick
this off once again and go ahead and
list all agents. Dan, we've got three
agents active, Blink and Sony for coding
tasks and a browser agent called browser
agent 17722. Let me know what you'd like
to do next.
>> All right, so we did get a end toend cat
generation here. That worked out great.
I would have liked to see our remix
feature working, but um let's go ahead
and see this video here. Okay, so great.
So this is the video generated by our
browser use agent. Let's just check this
out.
Okay,
the great part about the system is even
with a crash like that, we can quickly
just restart and we have our recent
files where the agents are logging their
work and we can just relist all of our
agents and have our primary agent spin
back up and get back to work. So, I'm
not going to dig into this too much
more. I wanted to showcase, you know,
what a multi- aent system looks like
when you start combining these different
systems. We have Gemini 2.5 computer
use, testing out capabilities, testing
out functionality. We have a nice multi-
aent system here where we can operate
with multiple agents and actually see
the results. We're using powerful clawed
code agents and then we have our actual
application that's getting built out by
our agents, right? We can do this now.
We can have them continue to deploy
against this to test to validate their
work. Let me just quickly pull down the
application here. You remember
throughout several pieces there, I
explicitly had my cloud code agents run
specific commands. They're directly
referencing some of these powerful
agentic workflows that have already been
built out. Right? We ran plan and we ran
build. They were able to directly use
these commands while being prompted from
another agent. Right? This makes it
really easy to extend their capabilities
and use more shorter concise natural
language to direct what they can do. We
can just quickly come in here kind of
validate some of the work they did
inside of the codebase. Our agents
operated this codebase for us end to
end. So if we come into the specs file
here, we can see our sor video
generation plan. Right? This was the
initial plan that we looked at that
actually executed all the work that was
built out. Right? Now, I should have
improved my prompt a little bit by
saying, you know, Sony, you're only
working on the back end, right? We did
get a great front end generated end to
end here, right? We have components, we
have our composables, and our blink
agent took care of that for us. And
inside of our backend here, if we open
up source, looks like we have some extra
files that were generated, but you can
see we have our primary interface there.
There's our main health checks. And
then, of course, inside of routers
videos, we have this great architecture
as was planned. And so we could have
tweaked any of this inside of our plan.
Classic fast API backend endpoints,
download content, so on and so forth,
right? All of this put together, built
out our sore video generator. This is
really a content generator. Thanks to
our agents here, we can just generate
these videos, right? Let's do a
cinematic scene wide shot of snowboarder
on massive mountain. Slow pan. Let's go
ahead and use 2 pro. I want 8 seconds.
Let's go ahead and try the portrait
view. Let's go ahead and generate that.
Thanks to our multi- aent orchestration
system, they built this out end to end
for us. So, we have this decent loading
screen. Of course, everything can be
improved, right? We can hop in the loop
after our agents have completed work.
What this is is another example of
orchestrating multiple agents, observing
our agents, and conducting our agents
with a highle interface. In this case,
we're using voice interface to
accomplish work. These are ideas that
you can be putting together, right? I
know someone in the comments is going to
say you can do this a lot faster if you
just type yada yada yada. There are a
bunch of, you know, conditionals to
voicebased workflows, but I've been
building out these multi- aent systems
for years now. Every single time I sit
down to experiment with what you can do
with the latest tools, what you can do
has progressed a great amount. Now, take
from this whatever you want to, but the
key ideas here are quite simple.
Voicebased agent coding is right around
the corner. If you're on the edge, you
can start building these out right now
to control and manage your fleets of
agents. Now, even without voice, right,
completely throw voice out the window,
right? You can use textbased workflows
and we can spin this up right now,
right? If we close this and we use this
workflow and instead if I say prompt uh
list all agents, check their status, I
have this interface for my agent to just
kick off our orchestrator agent and get
work done right away. So you can see
that's just we're blasting through all
this work here. All this stuff is
happening very quickly, very rapidly. No
voice response. It's all text. Okay.
Whatever system you want to build, make
sure you have text, make sure you have
voice. You want to expand the inputs
that you can have to your system so that
you can satisfy the feedback loop of
your entire multi- aent orchestrated
system, right? You want to build for
you, your team, and your agents at the
same time. Make sure that your outputs
of your system wrap all the way back
into your inputs. Make sure that your
agents can receive the feedback from
your system. All right, we have a
promptbased workflow. Right, let me just
clear that out again and show that to
you. Right, if we hit up, you can see I
have a entire workflow for this tool
that can be activated just with passing
in a prompt. Why is that? It's it's so I
can expose it to our agent so that our
agent can test it all for us. Last but
not least, we had our multi-agent
observability system to help us actually
monitor all of our clawed code specific
agents. You can really plug in any agent
you want to this. Right now, this just
supports claw code. I'm going to leave
the multi- aent observability codebase
linked in the description. It's based
right on cloud code hooks. We've talked
about this on the channel in the past.
That's going to be available there for
you. And if you want to push your
agentic coding abilities even further,
if you want to continuously start moving
from inloop to outloop, I have one last
thing to offer you. Many engineers
already know what this is if you've been
watching the channel. I want to pitch to
you tactical agentic coding before the
early bird deal runs out here on
Wednesday. Tactical agentic coding is my
take on how you can push far beyond AI
coding and vibe coding with advanced
agentic engineering so powerful that
your codebase runs itself. Now the ideas
here we've been talking about on the
channel over and over. We take those
ideas and we push them even further. Now
let me be super clear here. This is for
engineers that ship to production. This
is for engineers that are looking for
that big edge in the generative AI age
with agents. All right, we know that AI
coding is not enough and there are a
bunch of big ideas here, but the most
important one is that you, the engineer,
are the bottleneck. It's not the tools,
it's not the models, it's not the
agents, right? As you can see here in
our multi- aent example, right? It's
about what we can do. How can we
orchestrate all these powerful tools,
right? And check this out. We have our
we have our uh let me just go and full
screen this. Hop back over.
All right. And so we can download the
thumbnail, of course. We can download
the spreadsheet. We can work with this.
This is going to be the beginning of my
uh content generation platform. Make
sure you like and follow if you're
interested in seeing where this goes. Of
course, we're going to be building the
whole thing with agents, and it's going
to be a great way for us to explore
different multi- aent architectures.
Anyway, back to Tactical Agent Coding,
right? It's very clear that the models
are great. The tools are fantastic. The
agents are there. It's about you, right?
It's about you and I. We are the
bottleneck. Now, let's push our compute
further. All right. So, the guiding
question here is what if your codebase
could ship itself? Obviously, here I'm
asking the question. So, I have some
type of answer for you inside of
Tactical Agentic Coding. Disclaimer,
this is not for beginners. If you're a
noob, if you're a vibe coder, this is
not going to be for you. This will be
over your head. The ideas are pretty
advanced in here. We have a big goal
inside of this course. My mission is to
transform you into an engineer they
can't replace. How do we do this? We let
go of the old ways of engineering to
master the new best tool for the job.
That is of course agents. Okay. The big
idea that we explore over and over is
that we build the system that builds the
system. You want to be more and more
operating on the agentic system that
then builds the system. Now, we just saw
that I just showed you yet another
example of that inside this experiment
here, right? I built an agent
orchestration layer and then I prompted
that layer to build the application.
Okay, I built an agentic system once
again on the channel in public, right?
This could have gone wrong a million
times and it did go wrong a couple
times, right? There's this is this is a
spectrum guys, right? We're we're
constantly improving. Think in the gray,
right? No, no one has the answers now.
But the people that are experimenting
and pushing things forward, they have
more answers than the others. Okay? You
know, you saw that here, right? We built
a system cloud code agents browser use
agents with Gemini 2.5 real time open
AAI API right we're putting together
powerful layers of compute to then build
the system for us okay you're going to
see this over and over and over
jumpstart that right you can master this
architecture right now inside of
tactical agent coding okay and you can
learn how to build it inside of every
single codebase that you build all right
so we have a couple big ideas in here
right we scale the core 4 and just to
mention this there are two courses
inside Tactical Agentic Coding. The
first one is the core eight lessons. If
you just want the core of the big ideas,
just get this one. After you purchase
Tactical Agentic Coding, you can then
come into Agentic Horizon and get some
additional lessons and you can vote on
the next three lessons that come up. All
right, so all the lessons are here. All
the details are here. Link will be in
the description for you here. Of course,
um we're back for phase two. Thanks so
much for all the kind words from every
engineer. I need to add a bunch of
reviews. You guys have been really
hammering the reviews. We now have over
500 engineers upleveling their skills
right now. And just to mention this, um,
the deal, the early room special is
almost over. So get in here before this
ends. All right? By the time you're
seeing this, this is going to be like at
down at 3 or 2 or 1 days remaining.
Okay? This deal ends Wednesday night. So
get in here. I am rewarding engineers
that see opportunity and invest in
themselves. That's all this is. This is
not a marketing trick. It is just here
so that engineers that invest in
themselves and want a good deal for it,
they act on it. Okay, this is completely
risk-f free. It doesn't happen often on
my channel thankfully, but every once in
a while, you know, I'll get the random
few commenters that think I'm some type
of internet scammer or some fake guru.
Um, none of this stuff exists without
serious engineering over and over and
over, battle testing my ideas. Why am I
saying all that? I'm saying that because
I think about the engineering
perspective. You have a full refund
guarantee before you start lesson 4
within 30 days. You get your money back.
I don't want you in here if you don't
want to be in here. There's no value in
that for me or for you. So, if you get
to the third lesson and you don't like
my style or you don't see the vision,
you get a full refund guaranteed. No
questions asked. No problem, no hard
feeling. This is tactical agenda coding.
Check out the FAQ. Check out the landing
page video to understand what this is
all about. Once again, this is for
engineers that ship to production. If
you are a noob, if you're just starting
your journey, this is not going to be
for you. Okay? Um, building something
for everyone means building something
for no one. If you've built products,
you know that you understand that. So,
multi- aent systems are here. You want
to be thinking in and, not or. Put these
tools together to do more than you ever
could before. So, as many viewers of the
channel know, cloud code is my primary
agent coding tool, but I'm constantly
battle testing it against Gemini,
against Codeex, against all these other
tools. And most importantly, I'm
composing them together. Right? The name
of the game with engineering right now
is is that engineers with higher output
are almost directly using more compute.
Okay? I've said it on the channel
before, I'll say it again. There is a
direct causal relationship between your
compute use and your engineering output.
Scale your compute to scale your impact.
It can feel very overwhelming right now
with the insane pace of innovation
coming out of all these labs. What does
that mean for us engineers? To me, all I
see is opportunity. That's why every
single Monday, I sit down to try to show
you what's possible, show you potential
futures, to give you a concrete take of
ideas I'm exploring to push my
engineering further beyond so that you
can adopt them for your own so that you
can take them, tweak them, and get some
advantage. All right? It's all about
your information advantage. There's so
much slop out there. All right? Um,
there's so much slop out there. There's
going to be so much noise, right? Focus
on the signal. Focus on channels like
this that are actually trying,
experimenting, pushing, combining. And
always remember that if everything falls
apart, the one big idea you can lean on
is in order to scale your impact, you
must scale your compute. This is the
name of the game. This is why agents are
taking off right now. This is what
matters more than anything. Use more
agents, use more compute, build your
multi- aent system. And no matter what
you do here, stay focused and keep
building.